varidesk.com 2017-05-17

# Privacy Policy | VARIDESK Standing Desks

We keep your personal information private and secure. When you make a purchase from our site, you provide your name, email address, credit card information, address, phone number, and a password. We use this information to process your orders, to keep you updated on your orders and to personalize your shopping experience.

Our secure servers protect your information using advanced encryption techniques and firewall technology.

To keep you informed about our latest offers, we may notify you of current promotions, specials and new additions to the VARIDESK.com site. You may unsubscribe from our newsletters by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email you receive from us.

When entering any of our contests or prize drawings, you provide your name, email address and mailing address. If you win, we will send the prize to the address entered and notify you by email. When you enter a contest or drawing you are also included in our newsletter list to receive notice of promotions, specials and new additions to the Sample Store site. You may unsubscribe from this news list by following the unsubscribe instructions in any email received. See our Privacy Policy for more details.

## USE OF COOKIES

VARIDESK.com uses cookies. Cookies allow you the ability to use features like the shopping cart, and also helps to personalize your experience by remembering preferences or parts of the website you’ve visited. We also use cookies to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and website, as well as helping to provide additional insight about user behavior so we can improve our advertising and communication.

Cookies are simple to disable. In Safari, go to “Preferences”, and then go to the Privacy pane and choose “block cookies.” In Internet Explorer, go to “tools”, then “internet options.” On the Privacy tab, under settings, move the slider to the top to block all cookies. In Chrome, touch the Chrome menu and go to “Settings”. In the “Advanced” section, click “Site settings” or “Content Settings”. Deselect “Cookies”. In Firefox, click the menu button and choose “Preferences”. Select the Privacy panel, and under “History”, change the drop down to “Firefox will: Use custom settings for history”. Under “Accept cookies from site”, select Never.

Please note that if you disable cookies in your browser, you may not be able to use VARIDESK.com to it’s fullest, and it may affect your ability to use other popular websites as well.

The cookies used on our websites have been categorized based on the guidelines found in the ICC UK Cookie guide. We use the following categories on our website:

 **Category 1 – Strictly Necessary Cookies:**  
These cookies are essential to enable you to browse the website and use these features. Without these cookies, your shopping cart would not work.

 **Category 2 – Performance Cookies:**  
These cookies collect information about how you use our websites. This data is used to optimize our websites to enhance the user experience. These cookies do not collect any personally identifiable information like name, address, phone number or financial information. This information is collected in aggregate.

 **Category 3 – Functionality Cookies:**  
These cookies remember choices you make while browsing, and give us the ability to serve relevant messages to our site visitors whether they’re on our website or on websites that we advertise on. These cookies do not collect any personally identifiable information like name, address, phone number or financial information. This information is collected in aggregate.

We also use 3rd party vendor re-marketing tracking cookies, including the Google Adwords tracking cookie. This means we will continue to show ads to you across the internet, including on the Google Content Network (GCN). We respect your privacy and are not collecting any identifiable information through the use of Google’s or any other 3rd party remarketing systems.

The third-party vendors, including Google, whose services we use – will place cookies on web browsers in order to serve ads based on past visits to our website. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to the VARIDESK.com website. This allows us to market our products and services to those who have shown interest in our service.

## OPT-OUT

If you do not wish to participate in Google AdWords Remarketing, you can opt out by visiting [google.com/ads/preferences](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences)

You can also opt out of any third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting [networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/)

## PRIVACY ON OTHER WEB SITES

Other sites accessible through our site have their own privacy policies and data collection practices. Please consult each site's privacy policy. Our Store is not responsible for the actions of third parties.
